oscarmini.com 2011-12-14

# Privacy Policy ~ OscarMini.com ~ Latest free browsing cheats, adsense, mobile & make money online tips.

Privacy Policy for  
www.nairahack.blogspot.com  
If you require any more information or have  
any questions about our privacy policy, please  
feel free to contact us by email at  
oscarstevefrank@gmail.com.  
At www.nairahack.blogspot.com, the privacy  
of our visitors is of extreme importance to us.  
This privacy policy document outlines the types  
of personal information is received and  
collected by www.nairahack.blogspot.com and  
how it is used.  
Log Files  
Like many other Web sites,  
www.nairahack.blogspot.com makes use of log  
files. The information inside the log files  
includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses,  
type of browser, Internet Service Provider  
( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages,  
and number of clicks to analyze trends,  
administer the site, track user’s movement  
around the site, and gather demographic  
information. IP addresses, and other such  
information are not linked to any information  
that is personally identifiable.  
Cookies and Web Beacons  
www.nairahack.blogspot.com does use cookies  
to store information about visitors preferences,  
record user-specific information on which pages  
the user access or visit, customize Web page  
content based on visitors browser type or  
other information that the visitor sends via  
their browser.  
DoubleClick DART Cookie  
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses  
cookies to serve ads on  
www.nairahack.blogspot.com.  
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it  
to serve ads to users based on their visit to  
www.nairahack.blogspot.com and other sites  
on the Internet.  
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART  
cookie by visiting the Google ad and content  
network privacy policy at the following URL -  
http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html  
Some of our advertising partners may use  
cookies and web beacons on our site. Our  
advertising partners include ....  
Google Adsense  
Commission Junction  
Widget Bucks  
Adbrite  
Clickbank  
Azoogle  
Chitika  
Linkshare  
Amazon  
Kontera  
These third-party ad servers or ad networks  
use technology to the advertisements and links  
that appear on www.nairahack.blogspot.com  
send directly to your browsers. They  
automatically receive your IP address when  
this occurs. Other technologies ( such as  
cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may  
also be used by the third-party ad networks to  
measure the effectiveness of their  
advertisements and / or to personalize the  
advertising content that you see.  
www.nairahack.blogspot.com has no access to  
or control over these cookies that are used by  
third-party advertisers.  
You should consult the respective privacy  
policies of these third-party ad servers for  
more detailed information on their practices as  
well as for instructions about how to opt-out of  
certain practices.  
www.nairahack.blogspot.com's privacy policy  
does not apply to, and we cannot control the  
activities of, such other advertisers or web  
sites.  
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so  
through your individual browser options. More  
detailed information about cookie management  
with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers respective websites.
